

## NILOOFAR BIGDELI

**Social Media Specialist** 

- +46 722-584-687
- /niloofar-bigdeli
- bigdeli.niloofar1992@gmail.com

#### **PROFESSIONAL SKILLS**

- Social media tools:
   LinkedIn Ads | Facebook
   Business Suite | Hootsuite |
   Sprout Social
- Digital marketing tools:
   Google Analytics 4 | Google
   Tag Manager | SEO | HubSpot
- Content creation tools:
   Adobe Photoshop | Adobe
   After Effects | Adobe
   Premiere | Canva
- UX/UI design: Adobe XD |HTML | CSS



#### **PROFILE**

As a seasoned digital marketer with a focus on social media and content creation, I bring more three years of experience in the digital marketing realm. Currently, I am exploring opportunities within Sweden's digital marketing landscape, aiming to utilize my skills to drive impactful outcomes and appealing content.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**



### Social Media Specialist 04/2021 - 10/2022 | Loop54 (FactFinder)

- Managed company SoMe accounts on <u>LinkedIn</u>, <u>Twitter</u>, and <u>Facebook</u>, overseeing content strategy and execution.
- Provided monthly content kits, ensuring consistent and engaging posts across platforms.
- Analyzed posts' performance, leveraging data to optimize future content strategies.
- Utilized cross-functional collaboration on SoMe campaigns, resulting in a >2x increase in CTR and a 20% decrease in CPC compared to previous campaigns.
- Achieved significant improvements in KPIs within one year, including a remarkable 114% increase in engagement, and 72% boost in impressions.

## Social Media Marketing Specialist 11/2018 - 03/2019 | Inverse Digital School

- Social Media Manager with a primary focus on <a href="Instagram">Instagram</a> and <a href="YouTube">YouTube</a> platforms.
- Developed and executed the monthly social media strategy, planning and creating appealing content to boost engagement and enhance brand visibility.
- Implemented effective micro-influencer marketing campaigns, driving a notable increase in website visits and expanding the company's online presence.

## Digital Account Manager 02/2017 - 09/2018 | Boomrang Digital Marketing Agency

- Overseeing the social media presence of multiple companies (e.g., <u>Sunich</u>, <u>Castrol</u>), each with unique objectives with a focus on Instagram.
- Developed content plans tailored to each company's specific goals.
- Facilitated communication with content creators to maintain high-quality content.
- Effectively supervised communication with users, fostering positive interactions and brand loyalty.

# PERSONAL SKILLS

Digital Fluency
Collaborative Team Player
Positive and adaptive thinking
Attention to Detail
Cross-Cultural Competence

#### LANGUAGE

**English** - Professional working proficiency

Swedish - Basic knowledge

Persian - Native

#### **EDUCATION**



#### Digital Marketing Specialist

2023 | Sälj & Marknadshögskolan | Sweden

#### Masters of science in Executive MBA

2016 – 2018 | Allameh Tabataba'i University | Tehran, Iran

#### Bachelor of science in Management

2011 - 2015 | Payame Noor University | Tehran, Iran

#### **CERTIFICATES**



- ChatGPT Prompt Engineering (2023)
- Foundations of Digital Marketing and E-commerce (2023)
- The Ultimate SEO Training 2022 + SEO For WordPress Websites (2022)
- Master Google Analytics 4 and GTM bassics (2022)

# OTHER RELEVANT EXPERIENCE



#### Event Manager

Boomrang digital marketing agency

- Managed and coordinated multiple marketing events, strategically inviting loyal customers of our clients as well as social media influencers.
- Designed engaging games and entertainment activities, aiming to enhance our clients' social media presence and foster stronger connections with customers.

### Business Development Manager Banowin

 Co-founded an eCommerce startup called Banowin with a mission to empower women in Iran who were unable to work in traditional social roles by providing a platform to sell their handmade products or food online.

